\c&H002EFFFF\MOST PEOPLE HAVE NO
\c&H002EFFFF\IDEA HOW LONG IT
\c&H002EFFFF\TAKES TO DOUBLE THEIR
\c&H002EFFFF\MONEY.
\c&H002EFFFF\BILLIONAIRES USE ONE SIMPLE
\c&H002EFFFF\MENTAL MATH RULE.
\c&H002EFFFF\IT IS CALLED THE
\c&H002EFFFF\RULE OF 72.
\c&H002EFFFF\TAKE THE NUMBER 72
\c&H002EFFFF\AND DIVIDE IT BY
\c&H002EFFFF\YOUR ANNUAL INTEREST RATE.
\c&H002EFFFF\IF YOUR MONEY SITS
\c&H002EFFFF\IN AN ORDINARY BANK
\c&H002EFFFF\ACCOUNT EARNING HALF A
\c&H002EFFFF\PERCENT, IT WILL TAKE
\c&H002EFFFF\ONE HUNDRED AND FORTY-FOUR
\c&H002EFFFF\YEARS TO DOUBLE.
\c&H002EFFFF\BUT PUT THAT MONEY
\c&H002EFFFF\INTO THE SP 500
\c&H002EFFFF\AVERAGING TEN PERCENT, AND
\c&H002EFFFF\YOUR WEALTH DOUBLES EVERY
\c&H002EFFFF\SEVEN POINT TWO YEARS.
\c&H002EFFFF\LET COMPOUND INTEREST DO
\c&H002EFFFF\THE WORK.
\c&H002EFFFF\FREE GUIDE IN BIO.